There's nothing to tell.
It's just some guy I work with.
You're going out with the guy.
There has to be something
wrong with him.
So does he have a hump
and a hairpiece?
Wait, does he eat chalk?
I don't want her to go through
what I did with Carl.
Okay, everybody relax.
This is not even a date.
It's just two people going out
to dinner and not having sex.
Sounds like a date to me.
I'm in high school,
in the cafeteria..
and I realize I'm totally naked.
I've had that dream.
Then I look down and I realize
there is a phone...
there.
- Instead of
- That's right!
Never had that one.
All of a sudden,
the phone starts to ring.
And it turns out it's my mother.
Which is very, very weird
because she never calls me.
He says, "Hello,"
I want to kill myself.
You okay?
I feel like someone pulled my
intestine out of my mouth...
and tied it around my neck.
- Cookie?
Carol moved her stuff out today.
- Let me get you some coffee.
- Thanks.
No, don't!
Stop cleansing my aura.
- Just leave my aura alone, okay?
- Fine, be murky.
- I'll be fine. I hope she'll be happy.
No, you don't.
To hell with her. She left me!
And you never knew she was a lesbian.
www.tvsubtitles.net